When Square announced their awesome and revolutionary idea "Augment Your Pre-Order", we all cheered.
Then a bunch of barbaric YouTubers started to gang up on this poor, defenceless, billion dollar company.
Three against one!
Come on, kinda like the Catholic Church condemning Galileo for um...
...yeah, I'm not sure actually what he did, but are these things really that different?
I'm here to tell you to pre-order every game.
Why should you risk it?
Well, first of all, you get a better game.
Wow, this exclusive weapon skin is making this game truly enjoyable!
Wow, I hate myself!
The pre-order bonus is historic, if you pre-ordered the first Mario, you would get an exclusive skin in online matchmaking.
"But what if the game is bad?"
Yes, but what if the game is good?
Yes, but what if the game is goo-
-Actually, you know what?
Let's take all the common complaints and just debunk them.
"Some games are broken at launch!"
Yes, but is that really a problem, though?
Isn't that part of the fun?
You know, some people buy broken cars, fix them, and sell them for a profit.
Ever considered doing that?
Of course you haven't, you lazy bastard.
"But the game publishers will split up the game into smaller pieces and punish the blah blah blah blah blah."
How is this your problem?
You are pre-ordering games, this will only affect people who don't pre-order games.
This is actually a good thing!
To those fellas, you will be on a pedestal.
You will be a GOD!
"But my favourite YouTubers told me to dislike pre-orders!"
Okay, picture your favourite YouTubers.
Have you ever seen them in the same room as Hitler?
No?
Okay, have you ever heard them officially state that they are not cannibals?
You haven't?
Don't take advice from Cannibal Hitler!
So, pre-order away.
And you can't prove I was paid for this video, because it was all cash.